{
    "id": "0f05019f71254de1938f362c76332a0c",
    "title": "Active And Passive Voice Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "He is ..................................... by his own friends.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "being deceiving",
                "being deceived",
                "deceiving"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Prince Hamlet ........................................ by the people.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "welcomed",
                "was welcomed",
                "has welcomed"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The proposal ......................................... by the committee.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "has rejected",
                "has been rejected",
                "had rejected"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I ........................................ much cause for anxiety.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "have given",
                "have been given"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Have my orders .............................................. out by you?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "carried",
                "been carried",
                "been carrying"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The story was eagerly ............................................... to.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "listening",
                "listened"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Our lives are ........................................... in anticipation.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "wasting",
                "wasted"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The tree ......................................... by the storm.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "was uprooted",
                "was uprooting",
                "uprooted"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The wounded persons ................................................ to hospital by the police.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "taken",
                "were taken",
                "had taken"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "By whom was this piece of composition ........................................?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "writing",
                "written"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}